Max, sorry to keep you waiting.
來 麥克斯 久等了
Here's your favorite hamburger steak.
是你最愛吃的漢堡排
Why is there more? Really.
怎麼還有啊 真是的
Hey, how could you drink first?
喂 你怎麼可以先喝
You were supposed to toast with me.
跟朕一起乾杯嘛
What? That's a non-alcoholic drink, right?
搞什麼 居然是無酒精
You should open it quickly.
快打開…
It's overflowing.
滿出來了
Tsk.
嘖
(Episode12: Everything They Have Brought)
(#12 他們所帶來的一切)
What's wrong, Max?
(今日主角) 怎麼了 麥克斯
You've stopped eating.
你的手停下來囉
MAN OF THE DAY Is the food not good?
(今日主角) 不好吃嗎
No, it's not. You cooked too much.
不是 是你煮太多了
How many portions are there? I'm almost dizzy from eating.
到底有幾人份 我吃到快暈了
And how did you manage to cook so much food in our kitchen?
而且你用家裡的廚房 怎麼做得出這麼多菜
The pizza and cake are handmade too, right?
披薩跟蛋糕也是手工的吧
You can't even finish this tiny amount. You're useless.
這麼一丁點還吃不完 太沒用了
This is a rare victory celebration for the hero, come on!
難得幫你辦勇者慶功宴耶 真是的
This pudgy beer belly can't fit much in, huh?
這個肥嘟嘟的啤酒肚 也塞不了多少東西嘛
Stop it.
住手
But your agility is quite impressive.
不過你的身手倒是挺靈活的
An agile fat guy.
靈活胖子
Fat guy.
胖子
Come on, I'm not fat at all.
拜託 我一點都不胖好嗎
I'm not fat, am I?
不胖吧
Hard to say.
難說喔
-I'm not fat, right? Right? -I'll slaughter you guys.
-不胖吧 是吧 -我要宰了你們
Fat guy.
胖子…
I admire you greatly.
朕十分佩服
You defeated Leo and Fred, and saved them as well.
你擊敗了雷奧和弗雷德 同時救了他們
You further influenced the future of the Kingdom and the Republic.
進一步影響了王國與共和國的未來
It wasn't just my strength.
並不是靠我一個人的力量
Without Yuria's help, I would have been sent to my death.
沒有尤莉亞幫忙 我只是白白送死
It's all her credit.
都是她的功勞
And thank you too.
而且也要謝謝你
I didn't… do anything special…
朕沒有…特別做什麼…
That's not true.
沒有那回事
You certainly did.
明明就是
Thank you.
謝謝你
Indeed, I cooked a bit too much.
確實有點煮太多了
We'll save the leftovers for tomorrow.
剩下的留到明天再吃吧
Alright, I'm starting to feel sleepy from eating too much.
好啊 吃太飽 我開始想睡了
If we invite Zenia over, maybe we could finish it.
只要邀潔妮亞過來 或許吃得完
Why don't you call her over now?
不然你現在叫她過來啊
Geez. I'm not going to invite her today.
真是的 今天不找她啦
Your Majesty, I'm terribly sorry.
陛下 實在非常抱歉
What happened, Zenia?
到底是怎麼了 潔妮亞
Well, the thing is…
是這樣的
I used my laptop to analyze the computer brought back from the Magic Bureau.
我用我的筆電分析了 從魔導廳帶回來的電腦
There's all sorts of data. I don't get it.
有各式各樣的資料 搞不懂耶
What is this?
這是什麼
Press it and good things will happen.
"按下去就會發生好事"
Okay then.
我按
YOUR FILES HAVE BEEN STOLEN
(你的檔案被偷光光了)
So it's what they call a computer virus, huh?
也就是俗稱的電腦病毒嗎
Anyway, it's all in the past, don't worry about it.
反正事情過去了 別在意
To be honest, I completely forgot about it.
坦白說朕完全忘了這件事
Thank you for your forgiveness, Your Majesty.
謝謝陛下原諒屬下
What is this celebration for?
是在慶祝什麼嗎
Could it be Mr. Max's birthday?
難道是麥克斯先生的生日
That's right, you don't know anything yet.
對了 妳什麼都還不知道
Why don't you take a look?
不妨看一下
Enough already.
夠了啦
And then there's this video that's all the rage.
再來是城中話題的這段影像
Can you help find a way to resolve it smoothly?
能不能幫忙想辦法圓滿解決呢
Due to the live broadcast a few days ago,
由於前幾天這段直播影片
LATEST NEWS, BESKER KINGDOM the relationship between the Kingdom and the Republic has changed significantly.
(最新消息 貝斯卡王國) (針對共和國陣營的應對出現變化) 王國與共和國的關係大幅改變
In response to changing public sentiment,
(最新消息 貝斯卡王國) (針對共和國陣營的應對出現變化) 順應民情改變
THE RESPONSE TO THE REPUBLIC HAS CHANGED DRAMATICALLY the government softened its attitude toward the Republic.
(最新消息 貝斯卡王國) (針對共和國陣營的應對出現變化) 王國政府對於共和國的態度軟化
The government eventually agreed to make it an Autonomous Region.
(最新消息 貝斯卡王國) (針對共和國陣營的應對出現變化) 最終同意今後將之列為自治區
THE FUTURE RELATIONSHIP BETWEEN THE KINGDOM AND THE REPUBLIC That scared me.
(王國與共和國的今後關係) 嚇死我了
MALE AGED OVER 20 But I'm glad it was resolved peacefully.
不過幸好和平解決了
FEMALE AGED OVER 20 So the hero is so strong, it's amazing.
(王國與共和國的今後關係) 原來勇者那麼強 超厲害的
MALE AGED OVER 30 He's pretty cool. He's pretty cool when he's on his knees.
有夠帥的 下跪也很帥
Mr. Max is really amazing.
麥克斯先生真厲害
He's very popular.
簡直大受歡迎
That's great.
真是太好了
It's no surprise that they could build streets and fortresses with so few people.
怪不得他們能靠零星幾人 一下子就打造出街道和堡壘
Come, please have some.
來 請用
Isn't our captain amazing?
我們團長是不是很厲害
Sorry, even the people of our kingdom contributed.
不好意思 連我們王國的人都有份
What are you saying?
說那什麼話
There's no distinction between the Kingdom and the Republic now.
現在已經不分王國和共和國了
After all, we are now the "Kingdom Autonomous Region".
畢竟我們現在是"王國自治區"
But are you willing to accept this?
但是這樣你們接受嗎
Didn't you originally want to create an independent nation?
當初不是想要獨立建國
None of us wanted to build a nation or make things that big.
團長跟我們沒有那麼無法無天 想建立屬於自己的國家
We're just trying to protect the land we've worked so hard to create.
只是想守護這塊親手開拓的土地
After all, the kingdom wanted to forcibly expel us and confiscate this land.
畢竟王國本來想強制驅逐我們 並且沒收這塊土地
They were willing to make a compromise, for which we are already grateful.
願意讓步 我們已經感激不盡了
But it's great
不過真是太好了
that people from both sides are working together to pave the way to the kingdom.
可以像這樣 一起打造通往王國的道路
There will definitely be many tourists, including those from the kingdom.
肯定會有許多觀光客 包含來自王國的
Our proudest feature here is the hot springs.
我們這裡最自豪的是溫泉
The hotspring contains the magical ore's power, which smooths your skin.
以魔礦脈的力量 讓肌膚等等的晶瑩剔透
Once the work is done, you should go and try it.
工作告一段落你們就去泡泡看吧
That's awesome.
太讚了
This road has made a lot of progress.
往前邁進了不少
It's just a little bit away from the town.
離城鎮只差一點點了
Captain.
團長
Should I start calling you "Region chief"?
是不是該改口叫"區長"了
No, that title doesn't suit me.
別這樣 總覺得不太適合我
Your injury was so severe, yet you can still move freely.
傷勢那麼嚴重 居然還能活動自如
You had a big hole in your chest.
胸口明明開了一個大洞
That was just a scratch.
那只是小擦傷
Stop lying.
少騙人
Didn't you have a time when you couldn't move at all afterwards?
後來不是有一陣子動彈不得嗎
You're really undead.
真的是不死之身
That being said,
話說回來
it was fortunate for the kingdom that Max appeared
當時我重新體悟到 勇者一行人的強大
when I realized the power of Hero and his gang.
對王國而言 麥克斯現身 算是他們幸運吧
If it was a one-on-one fight between you and Fred,
如果是跟弗雷德單挑
you would definitely win, right?
絕對是團長會贏 對吧
That's hard to say.
這可難說
But winning alone is not enough.
不過光是那樣還不行
Because of them, we can shake hands and make peace with the kingdom.
能像這樣與王國握手言和 都是他們的功勞
I couldn't have done it alone.
憑我自己一人肯定辦不到
The hero is really amazing.
勇者果然厲害
Come on, former Republic Gamma, now Gamma Autonomous Region.
來吧 剛瑪共和國… 如今是剛瑪自治區
We still have a ton of work to do.
要做的事情還堆積如山呢
Let's get to work.
努力吧
Can you help find a way to resolve it smoothly?
能不能幫忙想辦法圓滿解決呢
It's news about Max again.
又是麥克斯的新聞
How many times are they going to replay this kneeling video?
這段下跪影片到底要重播多少次
But everyone knows.
不過大家都知道
You are the one who fought for the kingdom.
為王國賭命戰鬥的人是長官
Chief, how is your condition?
長官 您的身體狀況如何
If you need rest, please look at this.
如果需要休息 務必看看這個
A few days ago, I found some very valuable data.
前幾天我發現了相當貴重的資料
What valuable data?
什麼貴重的資料
What?
什麼
Then I will take my leave first.
那麼屬下先告辭了
Hello everyone, I'm Mackie.
大家好 我是麥奇
Please subscribe to the channel and like the video.
麻煩大家訂閱頻道 按一下好評
Today, we're going to put this candy into the Coke.
今天要把這個糖果放進可樂
The video and audio quality are terrible.
畫質跟音質都爛到不行
He is simply copying the contents of others who overdo it.
內容都是別人做過的 根本沒下苦心
And he's terrible at hosting.
而且很不會主持
Please subscribe to the channel.
麻煩大家訂閱頻道
Why is the video being shot from such a distance?
為什麼要隔這麼遠拍
SUPER DELICIOUS DESSERT REVIEW Convenience store desserts are super yummy.
(超美味甜點評比) 超商甜點超好吃
Feel free to contact me for business cooperation.
歡迎隨時找我業配
It would be best if a company commissions you.
最好會有企業委託你啦
Did you get me in the shot?
有沒有拍到朕
He actually forced that woman to shoot a video.
居然逼那個女的拍片
That guy is absolutely terrible.
那傢伙真是差勁透頂
Your face is very scary.
你的臉長得很嚇人
I'm self-aware.
我有自知之明
You should learn from me.
看我啦
Today, I also provided a happy topic
我今天也為了嫉妒麥克斯的長官
out of jealousy for Max's commander.
提供了開心的話題
The chief must be very grateful to me now.
長官現在一定很感謝我
Am I learning fast?
這樣我是不是學得很快啊
In all aspects…
就是…各種方面
I'm really something.
我也真是的
Stop shooting, stop shooting.
拍屁啊 別再拍了
This is really unpleasant.
真是令人不悅
Gamma Autonomous Region? Don't joke around.
什麼剛瑪自治區 別開玩笑了
There's no choice. After all, we can't go against public opinion.
這也沒辦法 畢竟不能違背民意
Public opinion, huh?
民意 是吧
I can't stand it. After a live video went viral,
受不了 只不過是因為那段直播影片
everyone began sympathizing with the hero and his team.
所有人就開始同情勇者一行人
It's their fault that Tratigo bought so many magical ore resources cheaply.
都怪他們 又有多少魔礦脈資源 被多拉齊格等國低價買走
Alright, don't talk about money hungry things.
好啦 別說那種見錢眼開的話啦
What?
什麼
It's quite regrettable for you.
對你來說算是挺遺憾的
But I didn't expect Max
但沒想到麥克斯那小子
to have the backbone to stand up.
還有骨氣挺身而出
It makes me see him in a new light.
令我有點刮目相看
The kingdom's people are also waiting for a chance to prevent this dispute.
王國民也一直伺機想停止這場紛爭
Mr. Max just created a great opportunity.
麥克斯先生正好製造了一個好機會
Is it okay to make them an autonomous region and give them special treatment?
不過列為自治區 給予特殊待遇 真的好嗎
They might get carried away and rebel again.
說不定又會得意忘形搞叛變
No, don't worry.
不 放心吧
Leo always returns favors.
雷奧向來有恩必報
He has always been like this since he joined the army.
從他從軍時一直都是這樣
Conversely, he also holds grudges.
反之就是有仇必報
That's why this happened.
才會發生這種事
Enough, quiet down.
夠了 安靜點
Stop arguing, let's continue the previous topic.
別吵了 繼續剛才的話題吧
It's not good to let him stand all the time.
讓他一直站著也不太好
Right, Chief Fred?
對吧 弗雷德長官
Your fighting was very brave.
你戰鬥的模樣真英勇
I saw it too.
我也看到了
So… Mr. Magic Bureau Chief.
那麼…魔導廳長官先生
Do you know that your actions and words were recorded by a drone?
你知道自己的言行舉止 被無人機錄下來了吧
I know.
知道
Then why didn't you destroy the drone immediately?
那為什麼沒有立刻破壞無人機
I thought it was a bird or something at the time.
我當下以為是小鳥之類的
You bastard.
混蛋…
Even if we ignore that,
即使撇除這一點
your magical attack seriously injured Captain Gelmof.
你仍然以魔法攻擊我的部下 蓋爾莫夫大尉 害他受重傷
I can't ignore this.
我可不能置之不理
But later he fought with Max and Leo,
但他後來與麥克斯和雷奧交戰
contributing to the peaceful resolution of this incident--
為這次的和平收場做出貢獻…
No, Max alone was enough, right?
不 那靠麥克斯一人就夠了吧
You're so stupid.
你真傻
If it wasn't for Leo and Fred fighting,
要不是雷奧和弗雷德打起來
Max definitely wouldn't have stepped in.
麥克斯肯定不會出面
This time, it's the credit of all the members of the hero team.
這次是勇者一行人所有人的功勞
Right, Fred?
對吧 弗雷德
From the moment I attacked the captain,
自從我射擊大尉的那一刻
I was prepared and willing to accept any punishment.
就做好覺悟 願意接受任何懲處
And as the second minister said,
而且如第二大臣閣下所言
I didn't make any contribution in this incident.
我在這次事件沒有任何功績
We are asking you to vacate the position of chief.
要請你讓出長官的寶座了
I have no objections.
我沒有異議
But it's not just about this.
但不光是這件事情
There's also the "accident" of the magic bureau explosion a few days ago.
還有前幾天的魔導廳爆炸"意外"
Oh my.
天啊
I was convinced it was Republic Gamma launching a terror attack,
我也完全以為是 剛瑪共和國發動恐襲
but it turned out to be a botched magic experiment.
沒想到只是魔導實驗出意外
This isn't funny, Minister Gremes.
這可不好笑 格雷姆斯大臣
I even told the media, "We will never forgive terrorists."
我還當著媒體的面大聲宣言 "絕不原諒恐怖分子"
For the Republic, the Kingdom appears to be deliberately fighting.
站在共和國的角度 等於是王國在刻意找碴
But Leo didn't question this.
不過雷奧沒有過問此事
For us, it's a big favor.
對我們而言算是幫了大忙
Let me ask you, Fred.
我姑且問一下 弗雷德
Do you have any clues about that accident?
關於那起意外 你有什麼頭緒嗎
I don't understand what you mean.
我並不明白您的意思
Never mind.
沒什麼
I heard Gremes say that you've been quite anxious lately.
只是我聽格雷姆斯說 你這陣子相當焦躁
It's understandable that you're eager for a resolution
與前夥伴對立 走向難料
after confronting your former companion and facing uncertainty.
渴望一個早日解決的契機也不奇怪
I see.
原來如此
Blaming the whole mess on a man with no value.
將爛攤子全推給利用完畢的男人
You're all so wise. Do as you please.
各位真是明智 隨你們高興吧
You really are impatient.
你還真是急性子
What? What's wrong?
什麼 怎麼了
Minister Gremes,
格雷姆斯第三大臣閣下
your warrant has been issued.
已發布了對您的拘捕令
No. Wait. Why?
不…等一下 為什麼
Because the explosion was Fred's doing.
因為爆炸是弗雷德幹的好事
Me? Why? It wasn't me.
我嗎 為什麼 不是我啊
Do you have evidence to prove that I caused the explosion?
你們有證據 證明爆炸是我做的嗎
What are you talking about?
您在說什麼
Your suspicion is embezzlement.
您的嫌疑是侵占公款
Em…
侵…
An unknown person sent data to mailboxes all over the world at random,
有不明人士 隨機向全世界的信箱傳送資料
LEDGER including the Kingdom's Magic Bureau's financial information.
(帳簿) 包含王國魔導廳的資金運用明細
FROM HERE TO THERE It shows that a part of the Magic Bureau's budget
(從這邊 到那邊) 其中顯示有一部分魔導廳預算
was transferred to your account through a virtual account.
經由虛擬帳戶轉入了您名義的帳戶
We have checked with the Magic Bureau's database.
已經與魔導廳的資料庫核對
This matter is confirmed.
確認此事屬實
Could you please come with us?
能請您來一趟吧
Really, it's so pathetic.
真是的 實在可悲
We have such a fool among our nine ministers of the Kingdom.
我們王國九大臣之中 居然有這種蠢材
You dare to say that I'm greedy.
還敢說我見錢眼開
You're the least qualified to judge me, Gremes.
你最沒有資格說我 格雷姆斯
Just give up.
乖乖死心吧
You should be grateful to just be accused of embezzlement.
只是以侵占公款了事 就該心存感激了
Fred, this…
小弗雷德 這…
It can't be you who did this, can it?
該不會是你做的
Who knows, I don't know anything.
天曉得 我什麼都不知道
Really, I've been set up.
真是的 被擺了一道
I didn't expect to have to leave the stage in such a boring manner.
沒想到會以這麼無聊的方式退場
But Fred, this is amazing.
不過小弗雷德 真是太好了
In the end, you and your companions escaped death.
最後你跟夥伴都逃過死劫
You also avoided a full-scale war. Congratulations.
還避免全面開戰 可喜可賀
War is truly disgusting.
戰爭實在令人討厭
Yeah. People who are still happy about going to war must be
是啊 開戰了還開心得起來的人
greedy people like you, who profit from the misfortunes of others.
肯定是像你這樣利用別人的不幸 貪得無厭的人吧
Yes.
是啊
After all, some people can profit from war.
畢竟有人可以因為戰爭獲利
Those who profit from this, however,
不過獲利的…
may not be mere humans.
說不定不只是人類
These chats are actually secondary.
這些閒聊其實只是其次
Fred, my original intention
小弗雷德 我本來啊
was to help you develop into a real man.
想把你培育成真男人
Change the hesitant you by freeing yourself
不被夥伴等等無聊的過往所束縛
from the monotonous past of companions and so on.
改變老是猶豫不決的你
Goodbye, everyone. Take care.
各位再見啦 保重
It's over.
結束了呢
After all, Gremes had endless negative rumors.
畢竟格雷姆斯那男人負面傳聞不斷
It was about time he got his retribution.
也該遭報應了
I didn't hear anything.
我什麼都沒聽說
You're too honest, so your words and actions are going to reveal it.
因為妳太老實 表情或態度肯定會露餡
Sorry for excluding you.
抱歉把妳排除在外
I'd also like to know
我也想問
what this farce is all about.
這場鬧劇到底是怎麼回事
Do you think Minister Gremes was behind the explosion at the Magic Bureau?
各位也懷疑格雷姆斯大臣 牽涉魔導廳爆炸嗎
What are you talking about?
你在說什麼
I thought it was said to be an accident.
不是說那是意外嗎
Or are you saying
還是說
you're convinced Gremes is behind it?
你確信格雷姆斯與那件事有關
No, let's leave it at that.
不 還是到此為止吧
After all, he's been very kind to me.
畢竟他對我關照有加
It's a pity.
真是遺憾
Didn't you intentionally leak those documents to expose Gremes' embezzlement?
不是你為了揭穿格雷姆斯侵占公款 刻意外流那些資料嗎
You're really quite something.
真有你的
No, I didn't do anything.
不 我什麼都沒做
What's wrong?
怎麼了
Nothing, I'm sorry.
沒事 失禮了
I just thought of something funny.
只是想起好笑的事
So gross.
好噁
So, I've played along with you for so long.
然後呢 陪你演了這麼久
You should fulfill my request now.
也該實現我的要求了吧
Of course.
當然
I had planned it this way from the beginning.
我一開始就是這麼打算
Fred,
弗雷德
we now have a vacant seat. It's quite a headache.
現在空了一個位子 真令人頭疼
You saved the kingdom again ten years after the demon clan battle.
繼十年前與魔族的戰役 你再一次拯救了王國
You deserve the position of the new minister.
想必配得上新大臣的位子
Although Gelmof will likely be indignant.
雖然蓋爾莫夫大概會憤慨不已
So that's what it's all about.
原來是這麼一回事
The video of the hero kneeling has over ten million views.
勇者下跪的影片 觀看次數超過一千萬耶
It's so funny.
超搞笑的
Really, if I'd known, I'd have stayed on my knees.
真是的 早知道就別跪了
It makes it hard for me to enjoy a can of beer in the park.
害我去公園喝罐酒都很難
That's my only pleasure.
這可是我唯一的樂趣
Hello, Mr. Max. We are from FREEDAY Weekly.
麥克斯先生您好 我們是FREEDAY週刊
I'm from Manchu Daily.
我是滿潮日報
-I'm from Women's Autonomy. -I'm from Weekly Spring Equinox.
-女性自主 -週刊春分
Due to your active performance a few days ago,
由於前幾天的活躍表現
you are now highly praised within the kingdom.
現在王國內對您讚譽有加
What were you feeling when you knelt?
下跪時是什麼心境
What's your reason for not favoring Leo or Fred?
不偏袒雷奧或弗雷德的理由是什麼
You seem to be unemployed at the moment.
您現在似乎沒有固定工作
What are your plans for the future?
今後有什麼計劃
You guys are such a nuisance.
煩死了
I'm busy, don't shoot without permission.
我很忙 不要擅自亂拍
He flew away. He is indeed a hero.
飛走了 不愧是勇者
-Quick, shoot it. -Go after him.
-去拍他啦… -追上去
Really, such a fuss.
真是的 吵吵鬧鬧
But it's good that peace has been restored.
不過算是恢復和平 也是好事
Yuria,
尤莉亞
do you want me to take care of him?
要不要換我來看著他
Is that so? Then I'll leave it to you.
是嘛 那麻煩你了
Max serves.
麥克斯發球
You're too naive.
太天真了
I'm back.
我回來了
What are those reporters up to? They've wasted my energy.
那群記者搞什麼 害我浪費體力
You're back, Max.
你回來啦 麥克斯
It seems you've managed to escape the media siege safely.
看來你平安逃離媒體包圍了
How did you know?
你怎麼知道
We saw it on TV.
我們在電視上看到了
Really?
真的假的
Max is exhausted,
既然麥克斯累了
so tonight we'll have the recently trendy Top Energy Don for dinner.
今天晚餐就煮最近備受好評的 "頂級精力蓋飯"吧
Good idea.
好主意
I want more garlic…
那我的蒜頭要多…
How long do you plan to stay here?
你們打算在這裡賴到什麼時候
Also, you and I are enemies, so it's strange that you live here.
況且你們身為敵人 還住在這裡就很奇怪了
Get out of here right now.
立刻給我滾出去
Anyway, the issue with the Republic has been resolved.
反正共和國的問題也解決了
And I've been resurrected.
我也復活了
What kind of joke is that?
開什麼玩笑
You just had a little fight.
只不過是上場戰鬥一下
It doesn't count as the resurrection of the hero.
哪算是勇者復活
You're far from the light you used to emit.
跟那時散發的光芒比起來差太遠了
I still need to take care of you.
朕還要繼續照顧你才行
Why would you jump to that conclusion?
到底為什麼會跳到這個結論
If His Majesty has such a plan,
既然陛下如此打算
then I will continue to stay here.
那我也會繼續留下來
As a secretary, I must ensure the safety of His Majesty.
身為秘書 必須保護陛下的安全
I won't do anything.
我什麼都不會做
Anyway, you get out now.
總之現在就滾出去
This is my room.
這裡是我的房間
Are you sure you want to say that, Max?
確定要說這種話嗎 麥克斯
Then you'll never taste the Top Energy Don I cook.
一輩子都吃不到 朕煮的"頂級精力蓋飯"囉
Not just that,
不只這個
there's also hamburger steak, chicken leg, pizza, and cake.
還有漢堡排 烤雞 披薩跟蛋糕…
Cook it today and leave. You said you'd cook.
今天煮了再走 你都說要煮了
All I want to do now is eat Top Energy Don.
害我現在只想吃"頂級精力蓋飯"
You still have a long way to go.
你還有待精進呢
I thought you guys were leaving.
不滾回去喔
Then let's toast to our reconciliation.
那就為和好乾杯吧
No, I don't want to drink with you again.
不要 我再也不想跟妳喝酒
Don't worry, I won't make the same mistake.
放心吧 我絕對不會重蹈覆轍
I don't want to, not even if I die.
我不要 死也不要
Please forgive her, hero.
你就原諒她吧 勇者
Everyone makes mistakes.
任何人都會犯錯
Hero. Max. Scandal.
"勇者 麥克斯 醜聞"
Stop it.
你給我住手
Then I'll take the picture.
那要拍囉
Sorry, I blinked again.
抱歉 再一次 我又不小心閉眼了
Again? Leo, have you had enough?
又來了 雷奧你夠了沒
I'm sorry.
對不起…
Anyway, I wasn't posing well just now.
反正我剛才也不夠好
Okay, perfect.
好 完美
Wait.
等一下
Then I'll make this pose. Or this?
那我就這樣…還是這樣
No.
不對
-Then like this. -Come on, just take the picture.
-那就這樣 -都行啦 快點拍一拍
Okay.
好 就是現在
Come.
來
Smile.
笑一個
With this, the journey of the hero has come to an end.
這麼一來 勇者之旅也要結束了
Although it was tough along the way.
雖然一路下來挺辛苦的
We've made it through.
總算是順利度過了
I won't see you guys again.
我再也不會和你們見面
This is what they call "peace", right?
那就是所謂的"和平"吧
Well, everyone, good job.
那麼辛苦了
Be careful on your way home not to get attacked.
回家路上小心不要被襲擊喔
Well, everyone, till we meet again.
那麼各位 後會有期
(Level 1 Demon Lord and One Room Hero)
《LV1魔王與獨居廢勇者》